module.exports = [

//5 CARDS
{
  "title": "5 cards",
  "tags": [],
  "questions": [
    {
      "answer": "7 of Hearts",
      "options": [
        "7 of Hearts",
        "1 of Hearts",
        "8 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the first card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "9 of Clubs",
      "options": [
        "8 of Hearts",
        "9 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the second card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "10 of Clubs",
      "options": [
        "5 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs",
        "2 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the third card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jack of Spades",
      "options": [
        "Jack of Spades",
        "King of Spades",
        "Queen of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fourth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "King of Diamonds",
      "options": [
        "Jack of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Diamonds",
        "King of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fifth card?"
    }
  ]
},
















//10 CARDS
{
  "title": "10 cards",
  "tags": [],
  "questions": [
    {
      "answer": "7 of Hearts", //1
      "options": [
        "7 of Hearts",
        "1 of Hearts",
        "8 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the first card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "9 of Clubs", //2
      "options": [
        "8 of Hearts",
        "9 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the second card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "10 of Clubs", //3
      "options": [
        "5 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs",
        "2 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the third card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jack of Spades", //4
      "options": [
        "Jack of Spades",
        "King of Spades",
        "Queen of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fourth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "King of Diamonds", //5
      "options": [
        "Jack of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Diamonds",
        "King of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fifth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ace of Hearts", //6
      "options": [
        "Ace of Hearts",
        "2 of Hearts",
        "3 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the sixth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "4 of Hearts",  //7
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "5 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the seventh card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "5 of Diamonds",  //8
      "options": [
        "3 of Diamonds",
        "4 of Diamonds",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eight card"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Queen of Spades",  //9
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "Queen of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the ninth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "6 of Hearts", //10
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "6 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the tenth card?"
    }
  ]
},













//20 CARDS
{
  "title": "20 cards",
  "tags": [],
  "questions": [
    {
      "answer": "7 of Hearts", //1
      "options": [
        "7 of Hearts",
        "1 of Hearts",
        "8 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the first card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "9 of Clubs", //2
      "options": [
        "8 of Hearts",
        "9 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the second card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "10 of Clubs", //3
      "options": [
        "5 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs",
        "2 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the third card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jack of Spades", //4
      "options": [
        "Jack of Spades",
        "King of Spades",
        "Queen of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fourth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "King of Diamonds", //5
      "options": [
        "Jack of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Diamonds",
        "King of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fifth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ace of Hearts", //6
      "options": [
        "Ace of Hearts",
        "2 of Hearts",
        "3 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the sixth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "4 of Hearts", //7
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "5 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the seventh card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "5 of Diamonds", //8
      "options": [
        "3 of Diamonds",
        "4 of Diamonds",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eight card"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Queen of Spades", //9
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "Queen of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the ninth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "6 of Hearts", //10
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "6 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the tenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "2 of Clubs", //11
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "2 of Clubs",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eleventh card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "5 of Clubs", //12
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "5 of Clubs",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twelfth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "9 of Hearts", //13
      "options": [
        "9 of Hearts",
        "10 of Hearts",
        "2 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "Jack of Clubs", //14
      "options": [
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "Jack of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fourteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "Queen of Clubs", //15
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fifteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "3 of Hearts", //16
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "5 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the sixteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "3 of Diamonds", //17
      "options": [
        "1 of Diamonds",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "3 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the seventeenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "Ace of Clubs", //18
      "options": [
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "Ace of Clubs",
        "King of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eighteenth card?"
    },
     {
      "answer": "3 of Clubs", //19
      "options": [
        "9 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs",
        "3 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the nineteenth card?"
    },
     {
      "answer": "6 of Clubs", //20
      "options": [
        "2 of Clubs",
        "6 of Clubs",
        "9 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twentieth card?"
    },
  ]
},

















{
  "title": "30 cards",
  "tags": [],
  "questions": [
    {
      "answer": "7 of Hearts", //1
      "options": [
        "7 of Hearts",
        "1 of Hearts",
        "8 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the first card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "9 of Clubs", //2
      "options": [
        "8 of Hearts",
        "9 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the second card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "10 of Clubs", //3
      "options": [
        "5 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs",
        "2 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the third card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jack of Spades", //4
      "options": [
        "Jack of Spades",
        "King of Spades",
        "Queen of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fourth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "King of Diamonds", //5
      "options": [
        "Jack of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Diamonds",
        "King of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fifth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ace of Hearts", //6
      "options": [
        "Ace of Hearts",
        "2 of Hearts",
        "3 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the sixth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "4 of Hearts", //7
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "5 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the seventh card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "5 of Diamonds", //8
      "options": [
        "3 of Diamonds",
        "4 of Diamonds",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eight card"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Queen of Spades", //9
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "Queen of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the ninth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "6 of Hearts", //10
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "6 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the tenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "2 of Clubs", //11
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "2 of Clubs",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eleventh card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "5 of Clubs", //12
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "5 of Clubs",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twelfth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "9 of Hearts", //13
      "options": [
        "9 of Hearts",
        "10 of Hearts",
        "2 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "Jack of Clubs", //14
      "options": [
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "Jack of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fourteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "Queen of Clubs", //15
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fifteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "3 of Hearts", //16
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "5 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the sixteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "3 of Diamonds", //17
      "options": [
        "1 of Diamonds",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "3 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the seventeenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "Ace of Clubs", //18
      "options": [
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "Ace of Clubs",
        "King of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eighteenth card?"
    },
     {
      "answer": "3 of Clubs", //19
      "options": [
        "9 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs",
        "3 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the nineteenth card?"
    },
     {
      "answer": "6 of Clubs", //20
      "options": [
        "2 of Clubs",
        "6 of Clubs",
        "9 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twentieth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ace of Diamonds", //21
      "options": [
        "Ace of Diamonds",
        "Ace of Hearts",
        "Ace of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-oneth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "4 of Clubs", //22
      "options": [
        "8 of Clubs",
        "Ace of Hearts",
        "4 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-second card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "10 of Diamonds", //23
      "options": [
        "10 of Clubs",
        "10 of Diamonds",
        "10 of Heart"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-third card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "10 of Hearts", //24
      "options": [
        "10 of Hearts",
        "10 of Diamonds",
        "10 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-fourth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "2 of Diamonds", //25
      "options": [
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "5 of Diamonds",
        "10 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-fifth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "2 of Hearts", //26
      "options": [
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "2 of Clubs",
        "2 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-sixth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "8 of Clubs", //27
      "options": [
        "2 of Clubs",
        "6 of Clubs",
        "8 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-seventh card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "6 of Spades", //28
      "options": [
        "6 of Spades",
        "6 of Hearts",
        "8 of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-eighth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "Jack of Diamonds", //29
      "options": [
        "Jack of Diamonds",
        "Jack of Hearts",
        "Jack of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-ninth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "King of Clubs", //30
      "options": [
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "Jack of Clubs",
        "King of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirtieth card?"
    },
  ]
},








//40 CARDS
{
  "title": "40 cards",
  "tags": [],
  "questions": [
    {
      "answer": "7 of Hearts", //1
      "options": [
        "7 of Hearts",
        "1 of Hearts",
        "8 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the first card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "9 of Clubs", //2
      "options": [
        "8 of Hearts",
        "9 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the second card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "10 of Clubs", //3
      "options": [
        "5 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs",
        "2 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the third card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jack of Spades", //4
      "options": [
        "Jack of Spades",
        "King of Spades",
        "Queen of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fourth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "King of Diamonds", //5
      "options": [
        "Jack of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Diamonds",
        "King of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fifth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ace of Hearts", //6
      "options": [
        "Ace of Hearts",
        "2 of Hearts",
        "3 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the sixth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "4 of Hearts", //7
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "5 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the seventh card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "5 of Diamonds", //8
      "options": [
        "3 of Diamonds",
        "4 of Diamonds",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eight card"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Queen of Spades", //9
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "Queen of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the ninth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "6 of Hearts", //10
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "6 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the tenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "2 of Clubs", //11
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "2 of Clubs",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eleventh card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "5 of Clubs", //12
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "5 of Clubs",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twelfth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "9 of Hearts", //13
      "options": [
        "9 of Hearts",
        "10 of Hearts",
        "2 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "Jack of Clubs", //14
      "options": [
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "Jack of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fourteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "Queen of Clubs", //15
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fifteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "3 of Hearts", //16
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "5 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the sixteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "3 of Diamonds", //17
      "options": [
        "1 of Diamonds",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "3 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the seventeenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "Ace of Clubs", //18
      "options": [
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "Ace of Clubs",
        "King of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eighteenth card?"
    },
     {
      "answer": "3 of Clubs", //19
      "options": [
        "9 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs",
        "3 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the nineteenth card?"
    },
     {
      "answer": "6 of Clubs", //20
      "options": [
        "2 of Clubs",
        "6 of Clubs",
        "9 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twentieth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ace of Diamonds", //21
      "options": [
        "Ace of Diamonds",
        "Ace of Hearts",
        "Ace of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-oneth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "4 of Clubs", //22
      "options": [
        "8 of Clubs",
        "Ace of Hearts",
        "4 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-second card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "10 of Diamonds", //23
      "options": [
        "10 of Clubs",
        "10 of Diamonds",
        "10 of Heart"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-third card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "10 of Hearts", //24
      "options": [
        "10 of Hearts",
        "10 of Diamonds",
        "10 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-fourth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "2 of Diamonds", //25
      "options": [
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "5 of Diamonds",
        "10 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-fifth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "2 of Hearts", //26
      "options": [
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "2 of Clubs",
        "2 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-sixth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "8 of Clubs", //27
      "options": [
        "2 of Clubs",
        "6 of Clubs",
        "8 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-seventh card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "6 of Spades", //28
      "options": [
        "6 of Spades",
        "6 of Hearts",
        "8 of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-eighth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "Jack of Diamonds", //29
      "options": [
        "Jack of Diamonds",
        "Jack of Hearts",
        "Jack of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-ninth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "King of Clubs", //30
      "options": [
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "Jack of Clubs",
        "King of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirtieth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "2 of Spades", //31
      "options": [
        "1 of Spades",
        "2 of Spades",
        "3 of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-first card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "Ace of Spades", //32
      "options": [
        "Ace of Diamonds",
        "Ace of Spades",
        "Ace of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-second card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "9 of Diamonds", //33
      "options": [
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "5 of Diamonds",
        "9 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-third card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "5 of Spades", //34
      "options": [
        "4 of Spades",
        "3 of Spades",
        "5 of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-fourth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "7 of Clubs", //35
      "options": [
        "10 of Clubs",
        "8 of Clubs",
        "7 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-fifth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "4 of Diamonds", //36
      "options": [
        "9 of Hearts",
        "4 of Diamonds",
        "1 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-sixth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "8 of Diamonds", //37
      "options": [
        "8 of Diamonds",
        "4 of Diamonds",
        "1 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-seventh card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "4 of Spades", //38
      "options": [
        "4 of Clubs",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "4 of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-eighth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "Queen of Hearts", //39
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "Queen of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-ninth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "King of Hearts", //40
      "options": [
        "King of Hearts",
        "Queen of Hearts",
        "Jack of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fortieth card?"
    },
  ]
},































//52 CARDS
{
  "title": "52 cards",
  "tags": [],
  "questions": [
    {
      "answer": "7 of Hearts", //1
      "options": [
        "7 of Hearts",
        "1 of Hearts",
        "8 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the first card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "9 of Clubs", //2
      "options": [
        "8 of Hearts",
        "9 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the second card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "10 of Clubs", //3
      "options": [
        "5 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs",
        "2 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the third card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jack of Spades", //4
      "options": [
        "Jack of Spades",
        "King of Spades",
        "Queen of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fourth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "King of Diamonds", //5
      "options": [
        "Jack of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Diamonds",
        "King of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fifth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ace of Hearts", //6
      "options": [
        "Ace of Hearts",
        "2 of Hearts",
        "3 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the sixth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "4 of Hearts", //7
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "5 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the seventh card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "5 of Diamonds", //8
      "options": [
        "3 of Diamonds",
        "4 of Diamonds",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eight card"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Queen of Spades", //9
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "Queen of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the ninth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "6 of Hearts", //10
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "6 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the tenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "2 of Clubs", //11
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "2 of Clubs",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eleventh card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "5 of Clubs", //12
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "5 of Clubs",
        "5 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twelfth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "9 of Hearts", //13
      "options": [
        "9 of Hearts",
        "10 of Hearts",
        "2 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "Jack of Clubs", //14
      "options": [
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "Jack of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fourteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "Queen of Clubs", //15
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fifteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "3 of Hearts", //16
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "5 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the sixteenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "3 of Diamonds", //17
      "options": [
        "1 of Diamonds",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "3 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the seventeenth card?"
    },
      {
      "answer": "Ace of Clubs", //18
      "options": [
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "Ace of Clubs",
        "King of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the eighteenth card?"
    },
     {
      "answer": "3 of Clubs", //19
      "options": [
        "9 of Clubs",
        "10 of Clubs",
        "3 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the nineteenth card?"
    },
     {
      "answer": "6 of Clubs", //20
      "options": [
        "2 of Clubs",
        "6 of Clubs",
        "9 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twentieth card?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ace of Diamonds", //21
      "options": [
        "Ace of Diamonds",
        "Ace of Hearts",
        "Ace of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-oneth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "4 of Clubs", //22
      "options": [
        "8 of Clubs",
        "Ace of Hearts",
        "4 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-second card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "10 of Diamonds", //23
      "options": [
        "10 of Clubs",
        "10 of Diamonds",
        "10 of Heart"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-third card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "10 of Hearts", //24
      "options": [
        "10 of Hearts",
        "10 of Diamonds",
        "10 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-fourth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "2 of Diamonds", //25
      "options": [
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "5 of Diamonds",
        "10 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-fifth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "2 of Hearts", //26
      "options": [
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "2 of Clubs",
        "2 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-sixth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "8 of Clubs", //27
      "options": [
        "2 of Clubs",
        "6 of Clubs",
        "8 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-seventh card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "6 of Spades", //28
      "options": [
        "6 of Spades",
        "6 of Hearts",
        "8 of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-eighth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "Jack of Diamonds", //29
      "options": [
        "Jack of Diamonds",
        "Jack of Hearts",
        "Jack of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the twenty-ninth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "King of Clubs", //30
      "options": [
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "Jack of Clubs",
        "King of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirtieth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "2 of Spades", //31
      "options": [
        "1 of Spades",
        "2 of Spades",
        "3 of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-first card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "Ace of Spades", //32
      "options": [
        "Ace of Diamonds",
        "Ace of Spades",
        "Ace of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-second card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "9 of Diamonds", //33
      "options": [
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "5 of Diamonds",
        "9 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-third card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "5 of Spades", //34
      "options": [
        "4 of Spades",
        "3 of Spades",
        "5 of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-fourth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "7 of Clubs", //35
      "options": [
        "10 of Clubs",
        "8 of Clubs",
        "7 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-fifth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "4 of Diamonds", //36
      "options": [
        "9 of Hearts",
        "4 of Diamonds",
        "1 of Clubs"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-sixth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "8 of Diamonds", //37
      "options": [
        "8 of Diamonds",
        "4 of Diamonds",
        "1 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-seventh card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "4 of Spades", //38
      "options": [
        "4 of Clubs",
        "4 of Hearts",
        "4 of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-eighth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "Queen of Hearts", //39
      "options": [
        "Queen of Spades",
        "Queen of Clubs",
        "Queen of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the thirty-ninth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "King of Hearts", //40
      "options": [
        "King of Hearts",
        "Queen of Hearts",
        "Jack of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fortieth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "3 of Spades", //41
      "options": [
        "9 of Spades",
        "3 of Spades",
        "4 of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the forty-first card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "5 of Hearts", //42
      "options": [
        "5 of Hearts",
        "3 of Spades",
        "9 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the forty-second card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "9 of Spades", //43
      "options": [
        "9 of Spades",
        "9 of Diamonds",
        "9 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the forty-third card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "Queen of Diamonds", //44
      "options": [
        "Queen of Diamonds",
        "9 of Diamonds",
        "King of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the forty-fourth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "8 of Hearts", //45
      "options": [
        "3 of Hearts",
        "2 of Diamonds",
        "8 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the forty-fifth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "8 of Spades", //46
      "options": [
        "8 of Spades",
        "8 of Diamonds",
        "8 of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the forty-sixth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "7 of Diamonds", //47
      "options": [
        "7 of Diamonds",
        "8 of Diamonds",
        "2 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the forty-seventh card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "7 of Spades", //48
      "options": [
        "1 of Diamonds",
        "8 of Diamonds",
        "7 of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the forty-eighth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "Jack of Hearts", //49
      "options": [
        "King of Hearts",
        "Queen of Hearts",
        "Jack of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the forty-ninth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "King of Spades", //50
      "options": [
        "King of Spades",
        "Jack of Spades",
        "Jack of Hearts"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fiftieth card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "10 of Spades", //51
      "options": [
        "10 of Spades",
        "Jack of Spades",
        "1 of Spades"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fifty-first card?"
    },
   {
      "answer": "6 of Diamonds", //52
      "options": [
        "6 of Diamonds",
        "Queen of Spades",
        "2 of Diamonds"
      ],
      "question": "What is the fifty-second card?"
    },
  ]
}


]
